<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fortnite on Joel&#39;s Diary</title>
    <link>https://joelrap.github.io/tags/fortnite/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fortnite on Joel&#39;s Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 16:05:16 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://joelrap.github.io/tags/fortnite/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Thursday, 4th June 2020</title>
      <link>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/06/04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 16:05:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/06/04/</guid>
      <description>Today I went for a bike ride. Then I did my Maths and English. I also made a Fortnite llama and then I had my lunch. After that I did my spelling test and got 97%. Later on I am going to see what is new in Fortnite with the dooms day device, because there is a live event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuesday, 2nd June 2020</title>
      <link>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/06/02/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 10:48:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/06/02/</guid>
      <description>Today I went a bike ride. After that I did my mMaths and English. I had to do a spelling test and got 100%. Later on I am going to have my lunch. Then I have a break before I am learning some french. Then I will play with my friends on Fortnite. I also got a new game called Tom Hero.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuesday, 26th May 2020</title>
      <link>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/05/26/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 10:08:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/05/26/</guid>
      <description>Today in Fortnite, Midas activated the dooms day device to destroy team shadow. Midas is the leader of team ghost and he is planning on flooding the map to win the war of team shadow and ghost. Personally I like team shadow the most, because the characters look better and I like the name shadow. In Midas’s room there is a suit that looks like the tempest skin. Tempest is known to control the storm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fornite Midas</title>
      <link>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/04/fortnite-midas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 15:07:28 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/04/fortnite-midas/</guid>
      <description>Midas is the best skin at Fortnite at the moment. I am 17 levels away from getting Midas. Midas is tier 100 and an evil agent. Anything Midas touches turns into gold. Midas lives in the agency with his henchmen. He has a Dooms Day device. Nobody knows what the Dooms Day device is.
I think the Dooms Day device is to destroy team shadow. So the whole Fornite community will have to wait and see.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
