<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>diary on Joel&#39;s Diary</title>
    <link>https://joelrap.github.io/tags/diary/</link>
    <description>Recent content in diary on Joel&#39;s Diary</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 16:05:16 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://joelrap.github.io/tags/diary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Thursday, 4th June 2020</title>
      <link>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/06/04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 16:05:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/06/04/</guid>
      <description>Today I went for a bike ride. Then I did my Maths and English. I also made a Fortnite llama and then I had my lunch. After that I did my spelling test and got 97%. Later on I am going to see what is new in Fortnite with the dooms day device, because there is a live event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuesday, 2nd June 2020</title>
      <link>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/06/02/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 10:48:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/06/02/</guid>
      <description>Today I went a bike ride. After that I did my mMaths and English. I had to do a spelling test and got 100%. Later on I am going to have my lunch. Then I have a break before I am learning some french. Then I will play with my friends on Fortnite. I also got a new game called Tom Hero.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuesday, 26th May 2020</title>
      <link>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/05/26/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 10:08:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/05/26/</guid>
      <description>Today in Fortnite, Midas activated the dooms day device to destroy team shadow. Midas is the leader of team ghost and he is planning on flooding the map to win the war of team shadow and ghost. Personally I like team shadow the most, because the characters look better and I like the name shadow. In Midas’s room there is a suit that looks like the tempest skin. Tempest is known to control the storm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monday, 18th May 2020</title>
      <link>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/05/18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 12:48:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/05/18/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I went for a walk with my dad, it took us over an hour to walk 5 miles. After that I got some v-bucks and I spent it on two skins: Vix and Commando. I played with my new skins with my friends online. After that I watched Modern Family with my tea, and then The Nut Job in bed.
This morning I went for a bike ride and then a walk with my brother and Dad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuesday, 12th May 2020</title>
      <link>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/05/12/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 11:25:24 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/05/12/</guid>
      <description>This morning I had my breakfast and then I went for a walk and bike ride. After that I did maths and English which was extremely fun, then I did some colouring (see below). In a bit I am going to do a spelling test and then have my lunch. I&amp;rsquo;m then allowed to play on my iPad until my mum gets home from work. Then I will do some more school work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thursday, 7th May 2020</title>
      <link>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/05/07/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 12:40:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/05/07/</guid>
      <description>Today I went on bike ride and then I had a walk after. I did some maths which was about shapes, I also did some English. Later I am going to do a spelling test. Then I am going to play on my iPad with my brother. I am also going to play on Times Tables Rockstars. Tonight I am going to do my piano.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wednesday, 22nd April 2020</title>
      <link>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/04/22/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 18:27:47 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/04/22/</guid>
      <description>Today I went for a walk with my family. Then I did some English. My topic is a long story about the King of Fishes who grants wishes. Next I did some maths which was about hundredths as decimals. I also went on Times Tables Rockstars. After lunch I did a spelling test. I also played outside with my brother Josh. I played CodeMonkey in the afternoon and completed seven levels on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thursday, 9th April 2020</title>
      <link>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/04/09/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/04/09/</guid>
      <description>Today I played Lego with my brother. Yesterday I was playing Roblox. In Roblox my favourite game is Pet Simulator, you can get money and you can buy different pets. In Pet Simulator, pets have levels, which are power ups that make the pets go faster.
I built a boat in Roblox which can float on water.
Me and my brother have been playing Minecraft and we built a great world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wednesday, 8th April 2020</title>
      <link>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/04/08/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/04/08/</guid>
      <description>I like reading Diary of a Wimpy kid books because they don’t have chapter’s. I also like watching Marvel films because they have my favourite characters in. I have Spider-Man toys. My favourite character’s is Spider-Man and Tony Stark because they are funny. My favourite film is &amp;ldquo;Spider-Man far from home&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thursday, 2nd April 2020</title>
      <link>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/04/02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/04/02/</guid>
      <description>Today I went for a walk and I found a new path. It was in a woodland. I went past a bridge and there was lakes either side of me.
I saw a den. It was in a small woodland. The den looked like a big castle and it was made out of sticks. Who do yo think was inside it?
I went past fields and homes. I walked just over 2 miles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wednesday, 1st April 2020</title>
      <link>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/04/01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/04/01/</guid>
      <description>I feel normal and calm. I played with my Pokemon cards. Later I am getting Fornite cards. I feel happy when I play Fortnite with my friends. I completed an Ancient Egyptians worksheet and I practiced my spelling. Next, I am doing Maths questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuesday, 31st March 2020</title>
      <link>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/03/31/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/03/31/</guid>
      <description>Fornite Fortnite is my favourite game, and this is why.
 I like the fact that I can play with my friends. I like building things. I like making friends. I like getting skins, because they look good. I like getting v-bucks, because I can buy something.  I like the fact that I can play with my friends on Fortnite. I have 38 wins on Fortnite. I got 2 wins yesterday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturday, 28th March 2020</title>
      <link>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/03/28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/03/28/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I did yoga, and played outside with my brother. I coded on CodeMonkey. I also watched Peter Rabbit.
Today I played on my iPad and then went for a walk. I tidied the garden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thursday, 26th March 2020</title>
      <link>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/03/26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/03/26/</guid>
      <description>Today I did PE with Joe Wicks, and played swing ball in the garden. I played hide and seek with my brother, Joshua. I feel happier today then yesterday. I am looking forward to playing Fortnite with my online friends tonight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wednesday, 25th March 2020</title>
      <link>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/03/25/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/03/25/</guid>
      <description>Today I made my Breakfast which was toast. I played in my garden as well. Then I did some yoga and I went on the treadmill. I feel energised, proud and fantastic. I am looking forward to doing my school work, my walk and playing fortnite. Hopefully I can play with my friends online. I played some scratch and times tables rockstars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuesday, 24th March 2020</title>
      <link>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/03/24/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/03/24/</guid>
      <description>On Tuesday I did Joe wicks PE session and football. Today I also did times tables and a Ancient Egyptian Dentist worksheet. I feel relaxed after this. I am hoping to play on fortnite later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monday, 23rd March 2020</title>
      <link>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/03/23/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://joelrap.github.io/post/2020/03/23/</guid>
      <description>On Saturday I went for a walk, then I played on my iPad. On Sunday I went for another walk with my brother Josh. I was on my bike. Today I did PE with Joe Wicks.
I also cooked my own lunch which was an omelette. If you want to cook an omelette then type in Google &amp;ldquo;Basic omelette recipe&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
